{
    "subject": "resource/Quicksand_(2003_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/distributor",
    "object": "resource/First_Look_Studios",
    "human_readable": "The distributor of the 2003 film 'Quicksand' is First Look Studios.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9752382040023804,
            "question": "What film was distributed by First Look Studios in 2003?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9697606563568115,
            "question": "What is the title of the film distributed by First Look Studios in 2003?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9274387359619141,
            "question": "Is First Look Studios a film distributor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8978565335273743,
            "question": "Name a film distributed by First Look Studios."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7747984528541565,
            "question": "What is the name of the studio that distributed 'Quicksand'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7667589783668518,
            "question": "Who distributed the movie 'Quicksand'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7435876727104187,
            "question": "Are there any other films distributed by First Look Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5266814231872559,
            "question": "In what year was the film 'Quicksand' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44469112157821655,
            "question": "What genre might the film 'Quicksand' be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3694951832294464,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the plot of 'Quicksand'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The distributor of the 2003 film 'Quicksand' is First Look Studios.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4876_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might the film 'Quicksand' be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4876_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year was the film 'Quicksand' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4876_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other films distributed by First Look Studios?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4876_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4876_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4876_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4876_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4876_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4876_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4876_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4876_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4876_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4876_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4876_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. In one of the files, it mentions \"First Look Studios was a former American independent film distributor, that specialized in home video releases of films and television series.\" And another file specifically talks about Quicksand being released by First Look Studios."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about First Look Studios, including its activities as a distributor for films such as \"Quicksand,\" which was released in various countries in 2003. This supports the statement that First Look Studios is the distributor of the 2003 film 'Quicksand.'"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several sources indicate First Look Studios specialized in home video releases of films and television series, while Quicksand had a theatrical release in multiple countries prior to a direct-to-video release.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}